[{"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What is this about, Ms my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " If he's not out, why are they here", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What calls?  I haven't made any calls", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "He was lying", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I thought he was lying", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " He told me he had done two others just like it", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "When he was seventeen", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The same as the firs two. Definitely a serial", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What clues?  I'm going to work my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Nothing", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "How did you know they were stockings", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Aw, my friend.  The Mouth gets a load of this and we got major headlines around the world.  deSalvo redux. The matter, you think they don't teach Latin in Catholic schools", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Who've I got to beat up except the messenger?  Does this give us anything to go on", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "See, now you've annoyed her.  You know she doesn't like you to touch me.  Does she, widdle wee fing!  Wuhve you so much!  Did you feed her", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "She doesn't lie!  You sure you fed her", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yes, I fed her.  If she says she's hungry, she's lying to you.  Again", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "She lies all the time.  Why would I say I fed her if I didn't", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "She doesn't lie!  You sure you fed her", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "That's what I don't know.  Why would you lie?  That's the problem... I can't understand why anyone would lie", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "If this is a first step in kicking me off the case, just tell me, to my face, sir, don't waste time being diplomatic", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Give him pompous son of a bitch", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "If we keep going and work till midnight..", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": ", my friend. This has got to..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "A man?  I thought he was a boy.  This last Christmas was the happiest Christmas I had in the last ten years... you know why?  It was the first Christmas in six years I was not in love.  Son of a bitch !  Who cares about marriage, the bed just gets crowded and noisy?", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Where's the john?  Let me clean up this mess, and get back to work", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "For God's sake my friend, leave her out of it.  You don't want her, you want me", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You've been perfect.  Don't spoil the symmetry", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I need he", "docId": "Copycat.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't care", "qsentId": 30}]